(Raj:)-Dude, I'm so sorry.
-Don't take this the wrong way,
(Howard:)but did you do this
for the insurance money?
(Stuart:)No. God, you sound
like the police, the firemen,
(Stuart:)my parents, my therapist
and the insurance company.
(Raj:)We're here for you, man.
Whatever you need, okay?
(Stuart:)Actually, I was wondering if I could
crash at your place for a few nights.
(Raj:)Sure, of course. Oh, actually,
Emily was gonna spend the night.
(Stuart:)You slept with her? Nice.
(Raj:)Well, I can't take all the credit.
She let me do it to her, but...
(Raj:)But I can always
call her and cancel.
(Howard:)Hang on.
I know a place you can stay,
(Howard:)and earn some money at the same time.
(Amy:)-Great.
-I just have to warn you,
(Howard:)it'll involve humiliation,
degradation and verbal abuse.
(Stuart:)So what's the catch?